{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Feng Shui Landscaping Service","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/62653/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62653,"taskName":"Landscape Designer - Feng Shui","taskDescription":"Design a Feng Shui Garden or Landscape","xmTaskDescriptor":"Feng Shui Landscaping Service","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Designer Feng decorator garden yard landscape","textMessagingName":"Feng Shui Lndscpe","rolloverLongDesc":"An oriental approach that looks at how layout \u0026 furnishings affect the flow of energy. The goal is to arrange things so that the yard's purpose or mood is supported by the arrangement of plants and features.","rolloverShortDesc":"Check the \"energy\" patterns of yard layout","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local Feng Shui Landscape Design services.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated consultants in your area.","htmlTitle":"Feng Shui Landscape \u0026 Garden Design \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Feng Shui Yard","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Feng Shui Landscape Design","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Landscape Designer - Feng Shui","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Feng Shui Landscape Project","urlName":"Feng-Shui-Landscape-Design","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Feng Shui Garden \u0026 Landscape Design Services in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Designer,Feng,decorator,traditional,consultant,space,Shui,landscape,yard, garden","emcCategoryOid":-12019,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9345,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62653/":{"taskOID":62653,"originalTaskOID":62653,"setID":9345,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4837,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which areas of your yard do you want to be designed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2735,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garden","answerDisplayText":"Garden","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4681,"questionDisplayText":"Other services","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What types of specific services interest you? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7224,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","answerDisplayText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7225,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","answerDisplayText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7226,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","answerDisplayText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7227,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","answerDisplayText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7228,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","answerDisplayText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7229,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","answerDisplayText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7230,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Advice on selling property quickly","answerDisplayText":"Advice on selling property quickly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7231,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","answerDisplayText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7232,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Five-element color consultation","answerDisplayText":"Five-element color consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4837,"questionDisplayText":"Square footage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which areas of your yard do you want to be designed? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2735,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garden","answerDisplayText":"Garden","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":924,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Back yard","answerDisplayText":"Back yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2661,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Front yard","answerDisplayText":"Front yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2735,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Garden","answerDisplayText":"Garden","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5675,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Side yard","answerDisplayText":"Side yard","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4681,"questionDisplayText":"Other services","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What types of specific services interest you? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7224,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","answerDisplayText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7225,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","answerDisplayText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7226,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","answerDisplayText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7227,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","answerDisplayText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7228,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","answerDisplayText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7229,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","answerDisplayText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7230,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Advice on selling property quickly","answerDisplayText":"Advice on selling property quickly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7231,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","answerDisplayText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7232,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Five-element color consultation","answerDisplayText":"Five-element color consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7224,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","answerDisplayText":"Comprehensive Feng Shui consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7225,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","answerDisplayText":"Space clearing of unwanted energies","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7226,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","answerDisplayText":"Chinese astrology recommendation for furniture placement","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7227,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","answerDisplayText":"Home or business site blessing rituals","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7228,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","answerDisplayText":"Identification of best new location for home or commercial properties","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7229,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","answerDisplayText":"Complete Feng Shui landscape advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7230,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Advice on selling property quickly","answerDisplayText":"Advice on selling property quickly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7231,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","answerDisplayText":"Enhance business for greater patronage and prosperity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7232,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Five-element color consultation","answerDisplayText":"Five-element color consultation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3915,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than $10,000","answerDisplayText":"More than $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}